What was the most important thing
that you learned about being an author?
The original working title of the book
was Enjoy the Walk or Enjoy the Journey,
and I feel like everyone's career, 63, I'm
still looking ahead for super exciting stuff as an
investor and a board member, but if I look back,
it's the skills I learned and the people I met
along the way that really mattered and changed my life.
It's not the job that you have, it's not the
company you work for, but if you have great
mentors and you have great people and you really
care about the people that you work with, helping
them get better, helping them move up the food
chain, helping them be successful, even if they
change careers outside of your role, I found that
to be the most rewarding. And so the real,
I just tell everybody, learn what you're doing where you
are today, enjoy what you're doing today, and it
will definitely come back and help you in the future.